Eslam A. Hugair

Full stack Web Engineer

Salah El deen St. Gaza Strip (+970) 592545262 eslam@engineer.com

EXPERIENCE

<u>Leadcart_</u>Ltd, USA — CTO

09/2018 - present

I started as Full Stack Engineer as LC(leadcart) & promoted to Chief Technology Officer in May 2018. I was responsible for developing features and using technology to enhance LC products and services that focus on external customers.

<u>Gaza Sky Geeks</u>, Palestine — Quality Assurance

06/2018 - 10/2018

I was responsible for making sure that every member of my team understands the application requirements, and implements them correctly.

<u>University Of Palestine</u>, Palestine — Teaching Assistant

09/2017 - 06/2018

Discuss and practice the abstract side of the Software Engineering materials, Ex, Programming, Data Structure, Software Architecture and networking in a practical way.

EDUCATION

University Of Palestine, Palestine—Bachelor degree

2012 - 2017

I have studied Software Engineering for five years in the University of Palestine and graduated first degree and I have been chosen to take a role as a teaching assistant for one year after.

PROJECTS

Tawasol — Web application

An IT company that offers Web development services, specialized in building web applications for customers and outsourcing web

SKILLS

Vanilla Javascript.
Reactjs(redux,mobx,contextAPI)
WebRtc,Socket.io
Nodejs
Express js
RestFul API Design
SQL(postgres,mySql,oracle)
NoSql(mongodb)
AWS(s3.ec2,ecs,fargate)

STATEMENT

I Started my career officially before two years in javascript after struggling with Java, and since then I started to develop my skill set in the web industry, I'm passionate about what I build and I hope one day I contribute in building a billion dollar business.

LANGUAGES

- English
- Arabic

developers and software engineers..

Zaino — Web application

A platform that intends to enhance the Adword customers user experience with the addition of a banners creator, the customers create the campaigns they want and create a banner for the ads and schedule the launch time, and just sit and watch their campaign statistics and performance.

<u>Drop shipping consultant</u> — *Chrome extension*

Doing reconnaissance and data scraping on certain websites for analysis reasons and provide suggesting for the customers using it.